Guide to the György Kepes papers M1796
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 15. Hungarian correspondence, publications, etc.
  - Bodri Ferenc, 1975-1977, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Correspondence. Bulk undated.
  - Hungarian work requests (Box 43, Folder 10)
    Correspondence. English and Hungarian.
  - Hungarian Museums, 1976-1978 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    Correspondence in Hungarian.
  - Hungarian Friends and Relatives, 1970-1979 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Hungarian Friends, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Assorted material, 1987-1989 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, drawings, and clippings. Majority in Hungarian, some in English.
  - Corvina, 1977-1979 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Originally in a folder of this title. Correspondence, relating to Corvina Kiado, which seems to be a Budapest gallery. Mostly in Hungarian, some in English.
  - Hungarian Letters, 1977-1987 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - G.K. Hungarian Text (Box 43, Folder 18)
    Typed material
  - Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    Bulk 1975-1980. In Hungarian. Contains two strips of photographic negatives.
  - Printed Material (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Printed material in Hungarian. Much of it has been hand-corrected.
  - Racz Pista (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Material in Hungarian.
  - Miscellaneous publications (Box 104, Folders 3-4)
    Most are about the arts. Includes two copies of the influential constructivist magazine Ma, one of which is original, and one reprint.
  - Hungarian newspaper clippings etc. (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - Hungaroton EP-23745 [7" record], 1 audio disc(s) (Box 105, Folder 30)
- Series 16. Publications: other artists, writers, designers, etc.
  - 16.1. Other artists A-Z & misc.
    Contains exhibition catalogs, articles, essays, pamphlets, and transcripts, as well as some photographs and correspondence. Includes material from MIT CAVS Fellows Michio Ihara, Piotr Kowalski, Rockne Krebs, Antonio Muntadas, Alejandro Otero, Otto Piene, Athena Tacha, Vassilakis Takis, and Wen-Ying Tsai. Other significant items include exhibition notices from the Lazlo Maholy-Nagy memorial exhibition at the Art Institute of Chicago in 1947, Piet Mondrian at Sidney Janis in 1951, and Jackson Pollock at Betty Parsons also in 1951. Some items are inscribed to Kepes.
    - A-B (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Richard Adler Xerox images (Box 15, Folder 7)
      8.5 x 11 Xerox paper.
    - Ars Electronica (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Bauhaus (Box 99, Folders 3-4)
      Mostly retrospective catalogs, but also contains Kepes' copies of Bauhausbücher series 9, 11, and 13.
    - Bob Beck. Light Shows (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Copy of promotional material on light shows written by Bob Beck for Color Control Co.
    - Jose Bermudez and NITINOL sculpture (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Correspondence between G. Kepes and Jose Bermudez re: NITINOL alloy. Includes 3 photographs of Bermudez's sculpture, 2 drawings, and 1 NITINOL wire in form of Kepes's name.
    - Max Bill (Box 99, Folder 5)
      Includes one catalog inscribed to Kepes.
    - Lowry Burgess. Memory and Utopia (Box 27, Folder 10)
      Photocopied manuscript for "Memory and Utopia" by Lowry Burgess.
    - C-D (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Michael Cain. Projected Exhibition of Light and Color (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Typescript proposal for an exhibition complete with drawings and collage diagrams.
    - Cunningham Dance Company Residency Proposal (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Walter Dackiw. Images of Cities and the Environment, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      Paper entitled Art, the Image and Constructed Knowledge by Walter Dackiw in May 1984 written for Kepes and Professor Lloyd Rodwin.
    - G-H (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Walter Gropius (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Dorothy Hood exhibition brochure, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      Exhibition brochure at the Marianne Friedman Gallery, Toronto. Opened October 9, 1976.
    - I-J (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Michio Ihara 1980-1997 and undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
      Published material and photographs relating to sculptor Michio Ihara, including the terminal for the Colorado Springs Airport.
    - Michio Ihara. Cyclelight., 1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Descriptive material and photographs about an interactive sculpture by Japanese artist Michio Ihara that was installed in Boston's City Hall Plaza, New Years, 1992.
    - K-L (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Kandinsky Yellow-Sound Project, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Materials concerning a proposed Kandinsky exhibit.
    - Lajos Kassak. Rediscovery of Lajos Kassak, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      Copy of an ARTNews article by Donna Stein about Kassak.
    - R.W. Keyes Patent Information, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Patent information for a Memory Controlled Shift Register Display Device. Registered to R.W. Keyes.
    - Piotr Kowalski (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Piotr Kowalski exhibition catalog, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Stedelijk Museum, Amsterdam, 11 April - 24 May 1970.
    - Rockne Krebs, 1969-1973 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      Materials were originally paper clipped together and marked "Krebs." - referring to Rockne Krebs - printed material and six photos. Two photos are of works by Krebs, others are from an exhibition Kepes worked on - works by Otto Piene and Wen-Ying Tsai.
    - Rockne Krebs (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Materials pertaining to light artist Rockne Krebs including correspondence, C.V., press coverage, typescript essay titled "Rockne Krebs' Three Works" by Nina Felshin, and one exhibition catalog.
    - Nathan Lerner - Talk for Institute of Design Reunion, 1947-05-11 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      Typescript with hand-written notes/corrections.
    - M (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Miroslav Malik, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Colin McCurdie. Connections: A Proposed Television Programme for Children, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - N-O (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - F.S.C. Northrop. Relation Between Naturalistic Scientific Knowledge and Humanistic Intrinsic Values in Western Culture, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      Photocopies of a book chapter
    - P (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Otto Piene (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Otto Piene. Tomorrow and the Rainbow: About Light, Art and Light Art., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Typescript of extended version of lecture given at Harvard University's Carpenter Center for the Visual Arts January 20, 1966.
    - Otto Piene. Proliferation of the Sun, Arts Magazine, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Copy of "The Proliferation of the Sun" by Otto Peine, Arts Magazine, Summer 1967. Includes 3 pages from different art press article.
    - PULSA, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Includes typed PULSA Boston Demonstration Report dated October 8-27, 1968, copy of art press article, copy of PULSA Boston Public Garden project catalog, and list of PULSA's research, exhibition, and teaching.
    - R-S (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Bruce Rich. "Electric" Interior Space (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Typescript of a piece written by Bruce Rich.
    - John Robert Ross. Poems as Holograms (Box 28, Folder 11)
      Mimeograph of a typescript of an article entitled Poems as Holograms by John Robert Ross.
    - Nicolas Schoffer and Cybernetic Light Tower (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Typed description of Schoffer's Cybernetic Light Tower for the Rond-Point de la Defense.
    - Sesson (Box 27, Folder 17)
      Copies of handwritten and printed material related to Japanese Zen monk and painter Sesson Shukei.
    - Simmons, Gloria/Draft (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Draft of a research report, with hand-written corrections.
    - Smithson Drawing, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Photocopy of a letter from Smithson to Kepes as well as a drawing on vellum of a "Mirror Ladder with Sticks + Vines."
    - Paolo Soleri. Minds for History, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      Manuscript of a publication by Paolo Soleri.
    - Hugo de Soto and Geny Dignac. Homage to G. Kepes, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      Printed material related to an art performance by artists Hugo de Soto and Geny Dignac.
    - T (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Vassilakis Takis [see also film, transcripts] (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Prodigal Genius, The Life of Nikola Tesla, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      Photocopy of an article by John J. O'Neil.
    - Wen-ying Tsai. Cybernetic Light Tower, Boston (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Description and Drawing of a Cybernetic Light Sculpture for Boston by Wen-ying Tsai.
    - V (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Victor Vasarely translated texts (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Typescripts with word counts; one has handwritten notation "translation" on top. Two duplicates titled "From-Color Integrated in the City by the Technology of Mural Surfaces," one titled "En Hommage a Alexandre Davillier" with title crossed out.
    - Victor F. Weisskopf. Science, Technology, and Society, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Typed manuscript of a piece of writing by Victor F. Weisskopf.
    - Christopher Willard. Periodicity and Paradigm Formation, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      Letter and attached manuscript of an article sent from Christopher Willard to Kepes. Willard wanted the paper published in the journal Leonardo.
    - Jekabs Zvilna. Rotation and Form, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      Published essay entitled "Rotation and Form" by Jekabs Zvilna, a professor at the University of Waterloo in Ontario.
    - Exhibition catalogs relating to light technology (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Kinesethetics at Howard Wise Gallery 6 December 1969-10 January 1970; Frank Gilette: Video: Process and Meta-Process at Everson Museum of Art, Syracuse, 1973; Vision & Television at Rose Art Museum 21 January-22 February 1970.
    - Typescript describing apparatus for multiple film projections, 1966-06-01 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Typed notes for The Electric Environment at Ontario College of Art, 1973-04 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Typed packet of notes, images, and diagrams for Exploration of Multi-Media Concepts workshop, part of The Electric Environment held at Ontario College of Art.
    - Light/Sound Workshop poster (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Poster for 'Light/Sound Workshop" at the Museum of Modern Art Oxford.
    - Government and the Future Welfare of the World, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      Photocopy of a speech given by an unnamed Secretary General of an unnamed organization at the Royal Palace, Amsterdam, April 28, 1973.
    - Other artists 1972, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
      Photographs and writings that are by other artists. Most are unnamed, but some materials are by Leif Brush and Keiko Smith.
    - Creative Collaborations Artist Architects, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      Information about an exhibition co-sponsored by various Boston-based visual arts organizations.
    - Lists of artworks by various artists (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Schreckhorn, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      Drawing entitled "Schreckhorn" Possibly by an artist named Jungfan.
    - Misc. art magazines, group show publicity, etc. (Box 102, Folders 2-4, Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Photography magazines, catalogs, etc. (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Architecture/urban studies magazines, catalogs, etc. (Box 103, Folders 1-4, Box 102, Folder 5)
      Contains magazines, reports, and scientific reprints. Includes Beiträge zum Bauen (possibly reprints), Ekistics, International Lighting Review, and others.
    - Design/advertising magazines, catalogs, etc. (Box 103, Folders 5-6)
    - Art/science/technology magazines, catalogs, etc. (Box 104, Folders 1-2, Box 103, Folder 7)
  - 16.2. Books, other artists
    Selected books from the Kepes collection. some can also be found in the library catalog. Many mention Kepes in the text, ando ne book jacket was probably designed by him.
    - Synthesis, other artist books (Box 119)
    - selected formative texts: Wyl / Symmetry 1952; Thompson / Growth & Form 1942; Marey / Movement (1895) (Box 119)
    - See All The People (Box 140)
      10 signed lithographs by Richard Sturm, 12 poems by Daniel Zimmerman. Printed in 1976 in edition of 30 with elaborate molded PVC housing. Kepes is mentioned in acknowledgements.
    - Books inscribed by author A-C (Box 120)
      Contains editions inscribed by James Ackerman, Merle Armitage, Pieter Brattinga, Marcel Bruer (as Lajko), etc.
    - Books inscribed by author C-J (Box 121)
      Contains editions inscribed by Charles & Ray Eames, Maya Deren (with enclosed note), Buckminster Fuller, Roman Jakobson, etc.
    - Books inscribed by author K-M (Box 122)
      Contains editions inscribed by Kevin Lynch, Sibyl Maholoy-Nagy, Lewis Mumford, etc.
    - Books inscribed by author P-T (Box 123)
      Contains editions inscribed by Octavio Paz, Otto Piene (see oversize for one additional), Athena Tacha, etc.
  - 16.3. Other artists: oversize
    - Otto Piene book (inscribed to GK) (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - MIT Art Collection (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Artts & Architecure magazine cover with Asawa wire sculpture, 1952-06 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Concepts of Educational Mobility (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Herman + Leews Assoc. - Design & Communications (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Art & Technology, Brooklyn Museum, 1968-1969 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - typescript proofs- exhibition catalog (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - 16.4. Juliet Kepes
    Gyorgy Kepes' wife was Juliet Kepes, an artist and illustrator.
    - A Celebration (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Two copies of a press release about an exhibition at Radcliffe in which Juliet Kepes participated.
    - Juliet Kepes book correspondence and clippings 1980s, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
      Includes letter and clippings re: children's book written by Juliet Kepes, and a few other items.
    - Juliet Kepes Exhibition Material, 1978, 1981, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
      Publicity materials and list of works for exhibitions involving Juliet Kepes and Marianne Fisker Pierce.
    - Children's Books 1977-1979, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
      Consists of correspondence and printed material related to Juliet Kepes' work as an illustrator.
    - exhibition promotion, articles, etc. (Box 96, Folders 5-6)
- Series 17. Biographies/CV/Press/Awards
  - Kepes press coverage photographs (Box 9, Folder 10)
    25 photographs reproducing press on Kepes from Life magazine and Boston Globe, possibly other sources.
  - Who is Who Biographical 1975, 1977-1978, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Correspondence and other files related to Kepes's inclusion in various Who's Who lists.
  - Publicity material, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    For gallery shows and other events.
  - Kepes Biography (Box 27, Folder 16)
    Photostat of a six-page typed biography of Kepes with hand-written corrections. Biography reads as if it might have been intended for an exhibition catalog or similar publication.
  - Gyorgy Kepes: Paintings Informed by Earth-Light, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    Manuscript and correspondence referring to manuscript of an Afterimage article by Robert Morgan on Kepes.
  - Biographical (Box 30, Folder 25)
    Material from Who's Who in the World and other biographical material about Kepes.
  - Awards, 1972, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    Clippings and press releases about Kepes winning awards. In a folder labeled "Wellfleet" originally.
  - Who's Who, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Letter from Public Affairs Manager of Who's Who in America and photocopy of a picture of a dining room.
  - Press Materials, 1966-1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Clippings and press releases/publicity materials, mostly related to the Center for Advanced Visual Studies.
  - Press Materials, 1972-1995 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Clippings, press releases, and promotional materials relating to Kepes.
  - City of Cambridge Resolution, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    City Council of Cambridge resolution acknowledging Kepes' many contributions to the City after his death.
  - G.K. Biographical Notes (Box 38, Folder 3)
    Kepes Biographical/Curriculum Vitae Information.
  - Gy. K. Introduction, 1970-1979 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    Printed material.
  - Kepes List pubs and exhibitions. Other vitae, undated and 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Various typed material related to Kepes' CV. Original folder title. Bulk undated.
  - For Gyorgy Kepes I (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Photocopy of a typescript about Kepes.
  - Bio/C.V. notes (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Certificates & awards (Box 190, Folder 6)
- Series 18. Miscellaneous
  - 18.1. Address book/planners [unfoldered]
    - Daily Reminders 1978, 1979, 1982, 1984, 1987 (Box 18)
    - Daily Reminders, 1988, 1989 (Box 19)
  - 18.2. Personal material
    - Invoice for home roof repair 1958 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Bills, 1966-70 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Stamps (Box 26, Folder 18)
      Small collection of various stamps from foreign countries.
    - Medical Notes 1988-1989, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Some material relating to Kepes' medical care, but much of it is generic published material.
    - Wellfleet Guestbook, 1950-1995 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Guestbook from the Kepes' house in Wellfleet, MA.
    - passport and SS card (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Guestbook for Gyorgy Kepes memorial service, 2002; 1 volume(s) (Box 97)
  - 18.3. Crate labels
    These labels were affixed to the original crates packed by Kepes.
    - Crate labels (Box 1, Folder 1)
      File folder with labels for crate A in pen, possibly in Kepes' handwriting. "LANGUAGE OF VISION (ILLUSTRATION) LIGHT BOOK - (NOTES) VISION+VALUE -PHOTOS ETC NEW LANDSCAPE (COPIES OLD PHOTOS) ENVIRONMENT LIGHT MODULATION" in green pen. "LOT: NOTES/MANUSCRIPTS - BOX 4" in black pen.
    - Crate labels (Box 9, Folder 1)
      File folder with labels for crate B in pen, possibly in Kepes's handwriting. "MISC. PHOTOS NEW LANDSCAPE PHOTOS + NOTES LIGHT MODULATION CARPENTER LIGHT EXHIBIT PHOTOS OF PAINTINGS-COLOR PHOTOS FORM OF THE CITY NOTES ARCHEOLOGICAL PHOTOS" in green pen. "LOT - SLIDES/PHOTOS BOX 1" in black pen.
    - Crate labels (Box 15, Folder 1)
      File folder with labels for crate C, possibly in Kepes's handwriting. "LIGHT BOOK PHOTOGRAPHS" in green pen; "LOT SLIDES/PHOTOS BOX 11" in black pen.
- Series 19. Media
  - 19.1. Video
    Some likely duplicates. Others may not include or refer to Kepes.
    - Stone, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Exegesis, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Pacific Ocean Deep Space Site Transmission, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Gyorgy Kepes, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 45, Folder 8)
      Contains a NYC Studio Interview, an Interview with Howard Wise, and "unknown clips". Runtime: 59:42
    - Gyorgy Kepes, 1977-05-03; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Part of the John Walley Commemoration. Runtime 50:38.
    - Fragments of "Explorations" for Gyorgy from Charles Forberg, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - 1st Day. G. K. Working on Window. Michio Ihara, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Gyorgy Kepes, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 45, Folder 9)
      Studio Interview NYC. Runtime 58:30
    - Staempfli Gallery, 1982; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 45, Folder 7)
      28 minutes.
    - Gyorgy Kepes Interview, 1982-04-07; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 45, Folder 10)
      Runtime 58:27.
    - Is Walter Gropius Alive and Well in the Late 20th Century?, 1989-10-05; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 46, Folder 3)
      Appears to be from a San Diego NEA Symposium. Runtime is 1:48:00.
    - Art Meets Architecture, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 46, Folder 5)
      "An Interview with Michio Ihara, Sculptor and Catherine Hunter, curator." September 22-November 12, 1989.
    - Chrysler LHS, 1994; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 45, Folder 4)
      Appears to be a VHS cassette. "Experience and Eloquent Expression of Form Following Function."
    - Inside the Visible, 1996; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 45, Folder 5)
      Published by Boston Institute of Contemporary Art. 30 min.
    - Drawing: The Thinking Hand, 1996; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 45, Folder 2)
      Written & Directed by Judith Wechsler. Louvre Museum / Les Films d'Ici. 53 Minutes.
    - Gyorgy Kepes - Studio Interview, New York City. One Hour Interview, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 90, Item 1)
    - An Interview With Gyorgy Kepes 4/7/82 "copy", 1982-04-07; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 90, Item 2)
    - Gyorgy Kepes - Studio Interview, New York City. 1/2 Hour Interview, 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 90, Item 3)
    - Staempfli Gallery. Sculptures Sonores Baschet 3/1/82. Devlin Productions, Inc., 1982-03-01; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 90, Item 4)
    - Gyorgy Kepes May 3, 1977. Duplicate!!! 1. Part of the John E. Walley Communication, 1977-05-03; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 90, Item 5)
    - Gyorgy Kepes. Interview With Howard Wise, August 1976. Color/30 Minutes, 1976-08; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 90, Item 6)
    - Kepes Center 11/91 Eger Hungary, 1991-11; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 91, Item 1)
    - Eger Museum 12/91, 1991-12; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 91, Item 2)
    - Naimark, 1986; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 91, Item 3)
    - Gyorgy Kepes Memorial Service at MIT. Kresge Auditorium. 1 Hour, 15 min. © Kepes Family & MIT, 2002-06-09; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 91, Item 4)
    - Profile on Gyorgy Kepes, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 91, Item 5)
    - Mate Gyula. Alkotasaibol [more information on label], 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 91, Item 6)
  - 19.2. Film
    - 1a-c. Kepes - Takis MIT Sessions CBS News 21st Century (Art) (Can #4) (AB-0, AB-4), 3 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 92, Item 1)
    - 2. Takis Interview. CBS News 21st Century (Art) (Can #5) (AC-0, AC-4), 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 92, Item 2)
      NOTE: Mold on film. Reel is isolated in plastic case and bag.
    - 3. Kepes Flame Orchard (Hoffman) 4/72 - sound. Optical Soundtrack for Optical prints (no picture) “Archive -> MIT”, 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 93, Item 1)
    - 4a-b. Kepes Flame Orchard (Hoffman, 4/72). A: Picture with Mag Stripe soundtrack B: Mag Sound Track. Original Film [bag says 7/17/07 "H06274"], 2 film reel(s) (35mm) (Box 93, Item 2)
    - 5. [damaged, oxidized or other chemical reaction, no visible image?], 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 93, Item 3)
    - 6. [blue leader, Back Bay Film Labs, Boston. Box stamped "work print" with "work" crossed out], 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 93, Item 4)
  - 19.3. Audio
    Some may not include or refer to Kepes.
    - Kepes, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Kepes, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - I.M. Pei Selected Works, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 46, Folder 11)
      MIT Museum Compton Gallery.
    - unlabeled cassettes, 9 audiocassette(s) (Box 46, Folders 12-20)
    - Magnetophone, Letter to Mr. Kepes, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Kepes at Museum. High Speed, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Kepes Interview for Pamphlet, 1967-12-20; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Compton Lecture, 1975-12-11; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Seattle with Bill Ritchie, 1978-05-24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Petaluma California, 1985-11-10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - MIT Morning Edition, "The Arts Remain a Large Part of the Curriculum at MIT", 1996-01-16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Michael Graves: The Sense of Boundary in Architecture (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Commercially issued lecture on audiocassette with slides.
    - Richard Meier: Interplay of Space and Place (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Peter Eisenman: An Act of Dissimulation (Box 47, Folder 3)